<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-21T01:54:14+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Upholdings</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Find the Next Apple - From Home!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/insights/2020/01/13/finding-the-next-apple.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Find the Next Apple - From Home!" /><published>2020-01-13T21:46:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-13T21:46:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/insights/2020/01/13/finding-the-next-apple</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/insights/2020/01/13/finding-the-next-apple.html">&lt;p&gt;Every investor needs two things to evaluate a potential investment: (1) the right questions, and (2) tools to answer those questions. Below are examples from Upholdings that we employ to deliver market beating returns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;our-eight-questions&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our eight questions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Does the company compete in a large market with a defensible position?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Are the staff talented and motivated to keep growing with the company?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Do the products lead their category in domestic and international markets?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Is leadership actively considering societal impacts from the company’s expansion?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Does the company transact profitably with all of its customers?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;What low cost marketing channels are available to access new customers?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;How does the team transform profits into shareholder value?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Are shares available at a clear discount to the company’s potential?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Company-released financial statements, annual reports, and transcripts are an excellent place to start answering those questions. But to figure out if it’s not just a good investment, but really a great investment, we have to go a step further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;alternative-data-you-can-access-from-home&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alternative Data You Can Access From Home:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;LinkedIn Premium has a tool that tells you how quickly a company is growing its employee base what types of employees they are hiring: is the company hiring salespeople and growing revenue, or is the company in investment-mode and hiring more engineers to build things?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Former employees: send a message to someone’s that has been out of the company for 1+ years; most people enjoy talking about their careers&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;appfigures: for free, they’ll tell you how many ratings by # of stars an app is getting each month on Android or Apple — the growth in review counts provide a great measure of the apps popularity and growth&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Google Sheet: build a basic financial projection — what numbers do you think the company will do? Insiders and analysts fail to accurately forecast their own business all the time, so go ahead and take a shot!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Google Alerts: setup an alert to receive a daily digest on all the news that’s coming out on the company.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are additional tools out there - email receipt tracking, private company revenue estimates - but you have to pay money for those!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the web has made it easier than ever to find the right answers, the hard part is exercising patience and only buying additional shares when the market offers a price that just can’t be beat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-upholdings&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Upholdings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upholdings is built for the next generation of investors. We manage a concentrated portfolio of the best public and private growth companies profitably reshaping big industries. We combine data-driven tools with expert-led insights to find the best opportunities to grow your hard-earned savings.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Every investor needs two things to evaluate a potential investment: (1) the right questions, and (2) tools to answer those questions. Below are examples from Upholdings that we employ to deliver market beating returns.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/uploads/more%20apple.jpeg" /></entry></feed>